GÖKMEN GÖRGEN

SKILLS CONTACT

Python, Rust, C++, Go Django, Flask, Flutter, Xamarin, Qt Ethereum, Solidity, Waves, RIDE gkmngrgn@gmail.com gokmengorgen.net Berlin, Germany

ABOUT

I started programming by contributing to GNU / Linux distributions then I involved in web projects with my Python experience. Later I developed mobile and desktop applications. Now I am interested in Blockchain technologies and Deep Learning. I am married and have a daughter. I don't think of relocation.

OPEN SOURCE PROJECTS

DOSH - A zero-dependency way to standardize all your development-related commands. Chainless - Free monthly planner that makes your life better.

Kuzgun - RSS reader for geeks who miss Google Reader

EXPERIENCE

Lead Software Developer Coachfrog AG Oct 2015 - Present

Berlin, Germany

I took on the role of team leader in a large project with multiple sub-projects. Each project used different technical skills such as Go, Nodejs and Python. The essential component of the project is a calendar and booking system.

Co-founder, CTO Radity GmbH Jul 2012 - Present

Zürich, Switzerland

We build tech startups, create digital products, deliver technology projects and put together tailored development teams for startups and grownups. SwissLife, Sherpany, and Coachfrog are some of the companies that we worked.

Software Developer Markafoni Oct 2011 - Jun 2012

Istanbul, Turkey

I worked in Zizigo ERP project for fixing errors, optimising code base, adding new features, etc. My first task was to send a notification mail to the customers about pending orders in Markafoni ERP. Also, I used Fabric for the deployment commands and Sphinx for writing documentation.

Software Developer Artistanbul PR Sep 2009 - Oct 2011

Istanbul, Turkey

Software Developer (Intern) TUBITAK Aug 2009 - Oct 2009

Kocaeli, Turkey

EDUCATION

Masters degree Management and Organization İstanbul Arel University

Diploma, Economic and Administrative Sciences Eskişehir Osmangazi University, 2005 - 2010

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

Coursera - Machine Learning, Algorithms DataCamp - Python Programmer, Data Scientist (with Python) Linkedin - Become a C++ Developer